[Music]
Hexes. Get your vile hexes. Only three
coins per box.
>> Only three coins. That's a deer in a
heart.
[Music]
Wonderful.
I'm so glad to be back in Abraa.
You know, I haven't been here in years.
Or has it been centuries? What time is
it? One of the two.
>> Hexes. Get your vile. Hex's.
>> New hex's check. Still need to visit the
slug merchant, the charm boutique, and
the slime spa. But first,
[Music]
the crystal ball repair store.
Hello. Uh, how much to get this old
beauty patched up?
[Music]
>> Need some repairs, huh, lady?
>> Oh, just some minor adjustments. You
know, the poor dear isn't as young as
she used to be.
>> Adjustments. Come on. This thing's a
total loss. Now, I could set you up with
a brand new top-of-the-line solid ruby
model for half of what it would cost to
repair this old junker.
>> This crystal ball saved me when
everything went down with a car
conclave. I am not abandoning it now.
You were around way back then. Whoa.
Then you should definitely invest in
some updated equipment. Check out this
mob emerald number.
Wait. What is that noise? Is it a sick
troll?
>> I don't remember this town having such
strange customs.
[Applause]
Do I have to save the day yet again?
[Music]
>> Hold you wizard junker.
>> How dare you insult her. She's one of
the finest crystals from the planet.
together.
[Music]
I need
I was there and it's still hard to
explain. I saw Raz getting dragged into
the portal gate. And since he was the
only person who knew where my parents
were, I freaked out. I couldn't lose him
to the Forbidden 5. Then knocked made
everything explode.
And suddenly I felt like my whole body
was turning inside out.
Then I landed somewhere I didn't
recognize. The Forbidden Five were gone.
But I had freed Roz. His injuries were
really bad and getting worse. He didn't
have long to live. He would only tell me
where my parents were if I took him to a
place that could heal him. It wasn't
close.
While I dragged him along, he trained me
and my skills got better like never
before.
We finally made it to this creepy place
called the Spectral Lands where people
who are departed passed through. It was
some kind of healing elixir in a well,
the only place you can get that stuff.
Roz got better and kept his promise.
I kind of wish he didn't. Raz made me
another promise. He said if I helped him
to undo the merge, to separate all the
combined realms, he would be able to
bring my parents back to life. So that's
what we were trying to do when we ran
into you and the ninja.
I used my objects to destroy that big
chaos dragon with some of that same
elixir.
I mean, I think it was my objects
bingjitsu that did it. Unless No, I
didn't help with that. It was all you,
Aaron. So, that's what you threw at the
dragon. Healing juice from some strange
well. We should probably stock up on
that stuff.
>> Yeah, it was not easy to get to. And
there were these ugly things called soul
suckers that attacked. And do you really
trust that Ros isn't lying? I mean, what
if reversing the merge can't bring your
parents back like he says?
>> I have to try because there's no other
hope.
But this doesn't work. My family is
really gone.
>> Hey, I get it. And that's why I'm here.
Because if we're doing something
dangerous, we're doing it together.
We're a team, right?
>> You bet we are. And remember, there's no
Raz in team.
>> Pack up. I know where we're headed.
>> How some desert animal tell you? There's
no one around for miles.
>> You are with us by my permission. Sora,
do not test me.
>> But she has a point, Roz. Even though it
merged like all the other realms, I
thought no one knew how to get to the
underworld. It's all mystical and secret
and stuff.
>> It is. And I now know who holds those
secrets.
>> I wonder what the ninja are up to.
>> Probably just another day at the
monastery.
[Music]
>> While this speed is optimal for rapid
travel, I feel we'd all be safer with
better piloting.
>> You try talking to her. Haha. My
airship, my rules. And the rule is I
drive.
>> Don't worry. I'll get us there in time.
>> That wasn't my main worry. Okay. For an
airship again,
>> Roby, she saved his life.
>> No one ever got me anything for saving
their life. Oh, my cake's coming back
up.
>> I told him not to eat cake for
breakfast.
Is it true?
>> Yes.
The great warrior will soon transition
out of this life.
[Music]
Ninja,
thank you for coming.
>> Eag, what can we do? There has to be
something.
>> Little one, you know the signs of
latestage wasting sickness as well as I.
There is nothing to be done.
[Music]
Members of my tribe, the dragons of the
Northern Spiral, are on the way to honor
my passing.
But they will not arrive in time. I am
glad to see one last time with my mortal
eyes, my final and greatest students.
>> We wouldn't be the ninja we are today
without the gift of your teachings,
Master Egot. It is you who gave me a
gift. You restored my faith in people.
It is a joy to have lived long enough to
receive this gift.
>> Where is my student Aaron?
>> Uh, master, he and Sora have chosen to
follow a different path.
>> That hurts my heart.
As a teacher, I was hardest on Aaron.
Not because of his failings, but because
he had the most potential of any ninja.
The world needs that potential
fulfilled.
You cannot let him go astray.
Master Lloyd,
>> the stories my family told about you, I
don't want them to end.
>> All stories must end,
but new ones begin.
I will move along to the next stage of
existence.
Whatever that may be,
a new adventure for an old dragon.
You are a credit to the fire tribe,
little one. A true dragon.
>> You inspired me to be a great warrior.
>> It is good to be a warrior, but one day
you will make a great leader.
run to my companion of many centuries.
The dangers we have faced, the life we
have shared. As the seven source dragons
are my witness,
I would not change a moment of my time
with you.
>> Goodbye, my love.
[Music]
Oh,
off.
[Music]
You're thinking about Aaron and Sora.
>> Eag was right. We have to find them.
[Music]
>> That is a very kind offer, Rayu. And I'm
sure living with you and the other
dragons in the monastery would be
delightful.
But this has been my home for centuries.
Eagle and I love these lands. I have to
stay here.
[Music]
>> Farewell, young Rayu.
>> Okay, let me just try to get this
straight. The place we're going to is
called Abraadoo.
>> Abracalabria,
>> right? which apparently can lead us to
the underworld where your source dragon
icon forges. But until about 3 hours
ago, you never said a word about it.
Then you walk off for a couple minutes
and come back with all kinds of answers.
Are you just making this up? You can be
honest with me.
>> I do not need to be interrogated by the
likes of you, Imperion.
>> Wow, pretty ungrateful for a guy riding
on a cycle I totally built for him.
>> I did not realize the price for these
vehicles would be uninterrupted
annoyance. Don't overinflate your value
to me, Anna.
You see anything cool out there, you
tell me right away cuz it's going to be
boring without you.
>> We promise to stay in contact.
>> Ruby is allowing us to use this city of
Temple's messenger dragons if the need
to communicate arises.
>> Hope those little dragons fly better
than Wildfire and the Bounty.
>> I heard that, Mr. Barfy. I can think of
no one more exciting to explore these
new merged lands with. Zayn,
>> if you come across any other strange
monasteries, let us know.
>> We will. But the only parameters of this
trip are for Pixel and I to share new
and exciting experiences together.
[Music]
>> You two enjoy yourself.
You said you were happy for Zayn, but
something tells me that wasn't the whole
truth.
>> Zayn and Pixel deserve some space to
themselves. It's just I feel like we're
falling apart. Master Woo always managed
to keep us together, to unite us, and I
I don't have that ability.
>> It's not your fault. The merge changed
so many things so dramatically.
>> Yeah, even when we find Missing Ninja,
it's not the same.
>> We've never had to help someone who
shattered their goodness before. He's
not only rude to me, but Cole and Kai
and everyone. But I can't lose faith in
him. And right now, he's our best hope
at bringing back Aaron and Sora.
[Music]
These all taste like sewage and not the
good kind.
>> I'll prepare another recipe.
I'm pretty certain his leg is healed and
he's faking it now.
I really hope he's leaving soon.
>> Was it you two clowns who tried to beat
my Galamorph record?
>> It was Kai, actually. He had this whole
plan to lure you with that game because
he knew it was your favorite when you
were a ninja.
>> Uh, quit acting like you know me, liars.
You could have heard about Galamorph
being my favorite game from anyone who's
ever met me.
>> We're not liars, Jay. We have pictures
of us together when you were a ninja.
You have a room here.
>> The administration had pictures, too.
And Roz told me all kinds of stories
about me working for him. That stuff can
be faked. You know what can't be faked?
Me not trusting anyone but myself ever
again. Well, I trust you. That's why I
believe you when you say Aaron's parents
are still alive. That's cuz they are. We
need to find them and bring them back.
>> Good luck with that. I told you they're
in a really weird place. the realm of
Lee. Doubt you'd ever get close.
>> But you could get us in.
>> Yeah, right. I'm only here until my leg,
which is definitely still massively
injured, heals. Then I have to get back
to my real job. I have someone paying me
a small fortune to find that Roz guy
your little buddy hangs out with.
>> So money is all that matters to you now,
Jay.
>> Of course not. Video games matter, too.
And drinking tea, that's not terrible.
Then we'll double what your other
client's paying you. I'll get it. I can
sell every scroll in the library if I
have to. And once we find Aaron's
parents, we need to find Roz, too, to
get Aaron and Sora away from him. So,
you'll get money and our help.
>> H. And I can bring Roz back to my
client.
>> If we get Aaron and Sora back, you can
do whatever you want with Roz.
>> Fine, but I can only get three of you in
the realm, Max. And one last thing, I'm
in charge. Okay. None of this master
ninja junk. Cool.
Cool.
>> What about your hurt leg?
>> Miraculously healed. Okay, then. Time to
prep. I'll need that frog guy to sharpen
all my weapons. And do you know where
there's a good dry cleaner?
[Music]
Hello. Welcome strangers to Abra
Calabria. Also, strangers are no longer
welcome in Abra Calabria.
I, Lord Raz of the Wildness, seek an
audience with the Pontifffects Magicus,
who holds information that is most
important to me. Maybe your homeland is
too wild for my sensibilities, Lord.
Because where I come from, which is this
humble city right behind me, no longer
welcome, means that welcome you are no
longer.
Oh, now you've irritated Torx and Zerat.
So, go away. Last time the twins got
angry, us wizards ended up in a
100red-year war. I found it most
inconvenient.
>> Yeah, Raz, I'm thinking maybe we better
leave.
>> No one denies me.
[Music]
>> Great. Just great.
The plateau was much lonelier than I
imagined. So I am reconsidering your
offer to come live here.
>> But my loneliness is not the only
reason. I once began your training to
become a ninja, Rayu.
>> And I am certain it will be Egot's wish
for me to continue.
[Music]
Come on. We're trying to leave. Don't
blame us for Roz's anger management
issues.
>> They must have been who attacked us last
night.
>> We were nowhere near here last night.
I demand an audience with the
>> What curse is this?
>> What happened here?
[Music]
Is this why they didn't want to let us
in
>> you? Where is the pot magicus? He alone
can direct me to the underworld.
>> You want the pots? There he is.
>> What has befallen this village?
>> If you just listen to me, this whole
situation could have been spared. But no
one listens to me anymore. or not since
that head shrinking incident in the year
45.
>> What are you talking about?
>> Well, I thought I had a spell for
normalsized heads, but boy was I wrong.
>> No, what happened to the villagers?
>> Oh, that we were attacked.
>> How do we know they aren't the ones who
attacked us?
>> Aaron, Sora,
sorceress, it's been so long.
to kiss you.
>> They are ninja and the ninja are allies.
Although I've never met that one and you
do look like a little angry catman. You
should try to smile more.
>> Sorceress. I'm assuming this place isn't
always like this.
>> Goodness. No. Last night, at the precise
moment the sun set, we heard these super
creepy noises and then we were attacked
by invisible enemies.
>> How did you defeat them?
>> We didn't. When the sun came up, they
were gone. And the victims now walk
around like in living sleep. One
attacker almost got me. My ball blew for
a second. I felt like something was
trying to suck out my life force, but I
managed to get away.
>> Invisible creatures sucking life.
>> Maybe those soul suckers you told me
about.
>> But they can't leave the spectral lance.
>> What did these creepy noises you heard
sound like?
>> Like that?
[Music]
They come back to finish the job.
[Applause]
[Music]